hey guys what's going on welcome to the
嘿家伙，欢迎来到这里
fourth Python with TV basics tutorial
第四个 Python与电视基础教程
video in the last video what we did is
上一个视频中的视频我们所做的是
we showed how we can use the keavy
我们展示 了 我们如何使用keavy
language for I suppose styling is the
我认为造型是语言
best word I can think of for it and so
我能 为它 考虑 的最佳词汇等等
we saw how we made our basic hello world
我们看到了我们如何创造了我们基本的问候世界
application and all we're actually doing
应用程序和我们所做的一切
in Python is returning label which is
在Python中是返回标签
referencing our key v file now I'm going
现在我正在参考我们的关键 v文件
to call this simple key V to this simple
把这个简单的钥匙 V称为这个简单
key v2 and now our actual key V file is
关键v2和现在我们的实际关键 V文件是
simple key B to zoom in here so now
简单的按键B 现在放大
we're going to go ahead and do is I'm
我们将继续努力，做到的是我
going to call this actually keep you
去打电话这实际上让你
video for now and this works as long as
视频现在只要这个工程
you only have one label now what happens
你现在只有一个标签会发生什么
if you want our term like three labels
如果你想要像三个标签这样的术语
like our login application or all kinds
像我们的 登录应用程序或各种
of things really and then also I was
的东西 真的，然后我 也是
talking about how you have parents and
谈论你如何拥有父母和孩子
children widgets and all this and how
儿童小部件以及所有这些和如何
you can customize based on that so
你可以基于此自定义
that's what we're gonna be talking about
这就是我们要 谈论的
here at least to start so we're gonna go
这里至少要开始，所以我们要走了
ahead and do is show how at least we can
提前做的是 证明至少 我们能做到
have two buttons for example so of
例如 有两个按钮
course you could say button like this
当然，你可以说这样的按钮
like lighting and then add this text
像 照明，然后添加这个文本
that should work no problem but but then
那应该没有 问题，但那时候
what if you wanted to have only buttons
如果你只想要按钮，该怎么办？
that were in relation to a specific
这与某个具体的事情有关
screen let's say or something like that
屏幕让我们说或类似的东西
so that's what we're going to cover here
所以这就是我们要在这里讨论的
so what we're going to do is we're come
所以我们要做的是我们来了
down here nationally we made one more
在全国范围内，我们再做一次
import and that's going to be widgets so
导入，这将成为小部件
we're going to do is from TV UI X dot
我们要做的是从电视 UI X点
widgets actually widget import widgets
小部件实际上是小部件导入小部件
now we're going to come down here and
现在我们要到这里来
we're going to say class and we're going
我们要讲课 ，我们要走了
to say class widgets and widgets is
说的类小部件 和小工具是
going to import for inherit rather from
将继承而不是从继承 导入
widget which is right here so that's our
这就是我们的小工具
widgets class now we'll come down here
小部件类现在我们会在这里下来
and our widgets class is actually just
而我们的小部件类 实际上只是
going to pass now if we were putting our
如果我们把 我们的东西 放在一边，现在 就要通过
TV kind of code within Python we would
我们会 在 Python中使用 电视类型的代码
put all that code in here
把所有的代码放在这里
but I'm going to show you how we can do
但我会告诉你我们该怎么做
it with the key B file instead for now
它与 现在 的关键B文件 相反
at least
至少
so let's just delete this up to here and
所以让我们把这个删除到这里和
now we're going to do is we're going to
现在我们要做 的是我们要
say we're going to use these little
说我们要使用这些 小
brackets and that's kind of to reference
括号， 这是一种参考
your parents I suppose so
你的父母我想是 这样的
we'll say widgets for the widget parent
我们会说widget的父窗口小部件
: 1 2 3 4 4 an indent and now we want to
： 1 2 3 4 4一个缩进 ，现在我们想要
do is we're going to say okay well
我们会说 好吗
within the widgets class so this is kind
在小部件类中，所以这是善良的
of like this is going to correspond with
这样的事情将会与之相符
this and it's going to know kvo is going
这并且它会 知道kvo正在发生
to know that we're doing that because
知道我们正在那样做是因为
it's the name is simple key v2 so it's
它的名字就是简单的键v2， 所以它是
simple key v2 is going to reference
简单的键v2将 参考
simple q2 kv then it's going to say ok
简单的q2 kv然后它会说好
well in this widgets a class what do we
在这个小部件中，我们要做什么
want and then it returns it based on
想要然后 基于 它 返回它
here where we're returning label at the
在这里我们正在返回标签
moment but we can just copy the paste
但是我们可以复制 粘贴
and now we want it to return widgets and
现在我们希望 它返回小部件和
it's going to reference this key v file
它会引用这个关键的 v文件
for information on widgets so within
获取有关小部件的信息
widgets we're going to say there's a
我们要说的小工具有一个
button and that button is going to have
按钮和 那个按钮 将会有
some parameters so those parameters are
一些参数， 使这些参数
going to be we're going to have size
将成为我们 将 有规模
we're going to have a position we're
我们 将有一个 我们 的位置
gonna have some text will have a color
会有一些文字会有颜色
and then font size and our actual size
然后字体大小和我们的实际大小
is the button width height so we're
是按钮的宽度高度，所以我们是
going to make this button 100 wide so
将这个按钮设置为 100宽
it's pixels 100 pixels wide 75 pixels
它的像素为100像素宽，75像素
tall now we have position this is a
高大，现在我们有这个位置了
little interesting in most GUI
在大多数GUI中很有趣
applications on the computers zero zero
计算机上的应用程序为零
is corresponding to where well normally
通常对应于哪里
it's the top left corner if you're
如果你是左上角的话
referencing let's say a try or a
引用让我们说一个尝试或一个
rectangle it's a top left corner now or
矩形现在是左上角或
if you're referencing a window it's
如果你正在引用一个窗口的话
still the top left corner is zero zero
仍然左上角是零零
so if we were to position a button at
所以如果我们在定位按钮
zero zero normally would be the top left
零通常是左上角
Cavey not the case zero zero is the
凯维 不是这种情况零零是
bottom left like a graph would be or
像图表一样左下角会是 或
something like that
类似的东西
not sure why they've done it this way
不知道他们为什么这样做
everything else like HTML CSS zero zeros
其他的一切都像HTML CSS零零
top left every GUI I've ever used or GUI
我曾经使用过的每一个图形用户界面或图形用户界面
development kit or something has always
开发工具包或其他东西 总是
been zero zero is top left I'm not sure
一直是零 是左上角我 不确定
why they did it I'm sure they have a
他们为什么这样做 我 相信他们有一个
good reason but they did so anyway
很好的理由，但他们反正这么做
zero zero bottom left keep that in mind
零点零左下方 记住这一点
too when you're positioning elements we
当你定位元素时，我们也是如此
when you position an element you say I
当你定位一个元素时，你会说我
want this element will say button to be
想要这个元素会说按钮是
at zero zero what will be at zero zero
在零点零点处将会是零点
is the bottom left corner of that
是的左下角
element so this button is going to be at
元素， 所以这个按钮 将在
zero zero so the bottom left corner now
零如此左下角现在
what if our window was 100 pixels tall
如果我们的窗户是100像素高
and we wanted that button to be exactly
我们希望那个按钮 是完全的
right at the top of our window well you
就在我们的窗口顶部，好吧
could position it at 100 pixels right or
可以将它定位在100像素 右侧 或
actually I'm sorry it would be zero for
实际上， 我很 抱歉，这将是 零
X and then why you would say let's say
X，然后为什么你会说 让我们说
100 pixels up but what would happen is
100个像素了，但会发生什么样的
since we're referencing the bottom left
因为我们正在 引用左下角
that button would be like the bottom of
那个按钮就像是底部
that button would be right at 0 100 and
该按钮将在0 100和
then the button would continue off the
那么按钮将继续关闭
screen up so you have to keep these
屏幕上，所以你必须 保持 这些
things in mind anyways for now 0 0 text
无论如何，现在0 0文本的 事情
the text of this button we're gonna say
这个按钮 我们要去的文字说
is Keeley the colors are an RGB a which
是基利的颜色是一个RGB的哪一个
is red green blue alpha alpha as a
是红色绿色的蓝色阿尔法阿尔法作为a
measure of opaqueness not transparency
衡量不透明度不透明度
some people say it's a measure of
有些人认为这是一个衡量标准
transparency it's the opposite of that
透明度与此相反
color we'll say is a green so 0 1 0 and
颜色我们会说是绿色的，所以0 1 0和
then full the opaqueness I suppose so
那么完全不透明 我想是这样
you can't see it font size will or you
你不能看到它的 字体大小 或 你
can see it or rather it's a solid font
可以看到它，或者说它是一个坚实的字体
size 40 ok now that's just one button we
大小40 OK 现在这 只是 一个按钮，我们
can save that hopefully simple give you
可以拯救那希望简单的给 你
two simple give you everything is good
两个简单的给 你一切都很好
let's run that and see how we do and
让我们来看看 我们 如何 做和做
yeah you can see we have a button here
是的，你可以看到我们在这里有一个按钮
and interestingly enough this button
有趣的是 这个按钮
actually is somewhat interactive we can
实际上我们可以有点互动
click on the button and you see there is
点击按钮，你会看到有
some sort of not a super cool event but
某种不是超级酷的事件，但是
there is an event when you click it
点击它时会发生一个事件
close this so we have that button now
关闭这个， 所以我们 现在 有那个按钮
let's say we wanted to add another
假设 我们想添加 另一个
button how might we do that well we
按钮我们 怎么能 做得那么好
would just do button :
只会做按钮：
and for simplicity let's just highlight
为了简单起见， 我们只是 强调 一下
all that copy paste and the size we're
所有复制粘贴和我们的大小
going to actually we're gonna call this
实际上 我们会打电话给这个
and then this one will be tutorial so
然后这个 将会是教程
it'll be a TV tutorials because
这将是一个电视教程，因为
tutorials is longer we need to make this
教程是更长的，我们需要做到这一点
a little wider so 170 should be fine
更宽一点，所以170应该没问题
position since this one was 100 pixels
因为这一个是100像素
wide we'll put this one at 100 starting
我们将把这一个放在100开始
at 100 zero tutorials good will make it
在100 零教程 好 将使它
a different color we'll say it's red
一个不同的颜色， 我们会说它是红色的
instead and font size can remain the
相反，字体大小可以保持不变
same let's save that let's run that and
同样让我们保存， 让我们运行该 和
now you can see we have these two
现在你可以看到我们有这两个
buttons TV tutorials now what I was
按钮电视教程现在 我是什么
going to talk about positioning them at
要谈论 他们的定位
the top but I think we'll actually save
顶部，但我认为我们会实际 保存
that for a later video but like I said
对于后来的视频，但就像我说的
before we can actually put some code
然后 才能真正放置一些代码
into here so for example let's say sighs
进入这里例如让我们 说叹息
okay uh size let's say font size 40 uh
好吧呃大小让我们 说字体大小40 嗯
we could say font size equals I don't
我们可以说字体大小等于我没有
know let's just say 80 divided by 2 just
知道我们只说80 除以2
to just a show
只是作秀
so font size is 80 over to run that and
所以字体大小是80以上来运行和
you can see that still worked so we were
你可以看到仍然有效， 所以我们是
able to put you know some logic in there
能够让你知道一些逻辑 在那里
and then later on you can reference you
然后你可以引用你
take font sizes a certain aspect ratio
采取字体大小一定的纵横比
of like the whole window so to speak and
像整个窗户可以这么说
then also when you're placing buttons
那么当你放置按钮时也是如此
you want to place a button right at the
要放置在一个按钮右侧
top you can use some mathematics how
顶你可以用 一些数学 如何
tall is our window how tall is our
身高 是我们的窗口 是 多高 我们
button go to window height minus the
按钮转到窗口高度 减去
height of the button boom that's your
按钮繁荣的高度，这是你的
position of the lower left corner of the
的 左下角的 位置
button so to speak so anyways um more on
可以这么说， 所以无论如何，我们 还有更多
that later those are just the quick
那以后那些 只是快速的
basics of of this but as you can see
这个基础知识，但你可以看到
we've actually already got some
我们其实 已经有了 一些
redundancy and font size now of course
当然冗余和字体大小
we could have in Python over here you
我们可以在 Python中在这里你
could say well you could just set a
可以说 你 可以设置一个
global variable and you'd be all find 80
全局变量，你会发现80
and that's true but as things get a
这是 事实， 但随着事情的发展
little more complex you might find that
你可能会发现更复杂的一点
this is the superior method again it
这是 再次 优越的方法
just kind of depends on what your kind
只是一种 取决于你的种类
of interests are what your comfort level
的兴趣是你的舒适程度
is what you're used to doing a lot of
是你用什么做了 很多 的
people like like with Python a lot of
人们喜欢用Python很多
the complaints of some of my
我的一些投诉
videos have been that I like to code too
视频一直是我喜欢编码的
much into one one file instead of
多到一个文件而不是
separating everything off into its own
把所有东西都分离出来
little file to me that's more
小文件对我来说更是如此
complicated more complex than necessary
比必要的 复杂 更复杂
to make a bunch of different little
使一堆不同的一点
files but to other people it makes a
档案， 但对其他人而言
whole lot of sense
很多意义
it just kind of depends on you know kind
它只是取决于 你所知道的那种
of what your style is and also the
一个什么样的风格 ， 也是
complexity of your program sometimes
有时你的程序很 复杂
this is going to make far more sense to
这 将会变得更有意义
use so anyways that's it for this
用这么反正就是它这个
tutorial
教程
if you guys have any questions or
如果你们有任何问题或者
comments on this video please feel free
对此视频的评论请 随意
to leave them below otherwise as always
离开他们 下面 另有一如既往
thanks for watching thanks for all the
感谢所有的 观看 感谢
support and subscriptions and until next
支持和订阅 ，直到下一次
time
时间